unscramblex.com 2019-04-28

# UnscrambleX.com - Privacy Policy

## Introduction

At Unscramblex.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit UnscrambleX.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Coverage

This Privacy Policy applies only within this website and other pages where this policy appears. This would describe and explain how we take care and handle your personal information you shared to us. By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on UnscrambleX.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include 

  * Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on UnscrambleX.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. UnscrambleX.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. UnscrambleX.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

## Third Party Links

You might find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

## Changes and Amendments

This private policy is in effect as of January 27, 2018. Be it remembered that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the site.
